[Music]
oh here comes
theur what the f is this he means what
the he's just too mad to say it what the
f Harold and Kumar that's not who we are
we're sorry there was a misunderstanding
what kind of misunderstanding breaks
wood a computer drives the bus we didn't
do you know why this gate is there to
stop people from coming on the L this is
the thin white and red that separates
the Dream Factory from you
we're coming on God damn it
coming on oh no no no all right
everybody be cool please these are cops
we don't want any trouble settle down
smells like a goddamn bonaroo in his
place sit down sit the down down sit the
down oh you chuckle heads oh everything
we are going to do what is called a nuts
and butts nuts and butts no no no I
don't want to do that sounds terrible
look everyone here we're not okay what
no no hey no no Hollywood what about it
sounds terrible
no we would have your opinion on law
enforcement I can't wait to oh I can't
wait to hear it I can't if you get
called randomly for a nuts and butts I
have a feeling I know who random is
there goodl
looking if you get called for a nuts and
butts here's what happens you grab your
ankles you drop your drawers you pull
your cheeks apart like it's the opening
of a movie at the El
capan and you lift your scrotal sack so
we can look underneath at the same
time keep going no say more
wo stop with the
[Laughter]
w